[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 28]
Hao Jie.
I'm back.
Liu Yang,
may this letter find you well.
By the time you read this,
I will have boarded a train
that passes through
the stations whose names
we've recited countless times,
and be heading to the south.
Before departure,
I met with Chen Hong.
Sorry for acting without your permission.
Please forgive me for any pertinence.
She agreed to give me 300 thousand yuan
so I can seek medical treatment
in the south.
In return,
I voluntarily withdraw
from this relationship.
Lately, I often ask myself,
since we first reunited
and got together,
if I have
ever truly loved you.
Every time this thought arises,
I'd feel a deep sense of guilt toward you.
I wish for nothing
but to survive.
To me,
you were just the last lifeline I grasped
when I sank into absolute despair.
Never did I expect you
to sacrifice so much for me.
I am so moved,
but I have nothing to repay you with.
As time went by,
I gradually discovered
that many new feelings
were taking root in my heart—
expectation,
possessiveness,
resentment.
Perhaps this is what people call love.
But even so, what can I do?
Other than continuing to be
a heavy burden to you,
I'm unable to give you a warm embrace
and a cozy life that other women can.
Just trying to survive
has drained all my strength.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
Also, please express my gratitude
to Chen Hong.
I sincerely hope the two of you
lead a happy life
and gain success in everything you do.
[Junlan Grand Hotel] [Friendly Reminder]
[Previously]
Coming!
Have a seat.
After starting dialysis,
I stopped producing urine.
My kidneys have shrunk,
so I dare not drink too much water.
How far along are you?
Less than three months.
Just about as long as I guessed.
Because of my illness,
Yang has been subjected to much suffering.
It's actually fine the way it is now.
In fact, I'm jealous of you.
Jealous of me being severely ill?
Yes.
I'm jealous that you have everything
but health,
like the love of a man.
Now, I only want to survive.
I'm in need of money.
I plan to go to Shanghai,
wait in line for a kidney donor,
and receive a kidney transplant.
If you agree to help,
I'll leave Yang immediately.
How much do you need?
When it comes to staying alive,
nothing is off-limits.
[Golden Imperial Dance Hall]
You go first.
The usual place.
Absolutely.
What are you guys talking about?
You can do that too?
I saw her palm that day. It was different.
Come on, give me your hand.
Look.
What do you see in my palm?
Big Fella.
Big Fella!
-Quite messy.
-You sure you can read palms?
Dong, come...
Yan'er, it's you!
When did you get back?
Several days ago.
Where is Dong?
No idea.
Dong didn't show up today.
He didn't?
We haven't seen Dong for days.
Your palm lines are messy.
I read hers before.
Look at mine now.
These lines...
Could something have happened to Dong?
What?
The third incense stick.
No more chatter!
Let's go look for him!
Let's go.
Is he in there?
No.
Did you search carefully?
Yes, I did.
Did you find him?
-No.
-Not a trace.
Dong!
Dong.
Did you find him?
-No. What about you?
-You guys found him or not?
No.
Are you stupid or what?
Could Dong be in here?
It's possible.
Dong!
Is he there?
No.
Let's move then!
[Welcome]
Go check the car!
Dong.
Come out, Dong.
Where are you hiding, Dong?
Any findings in the back?
Dong!
Dong.
Let's check over there!
Inquire properly!
Ask each of them!
Sir, have you seen this man?
Stop eating. Take a look at this.
Have you seen this man?
Eyes on the photo, not me!
Have you seen this person?
Have you seen this man?
He's named Dong.
Is it good?
Good.
Talking to you is such a pain.
Never seen him, huh?
Why is it so hard to talk to you?
I'm taking all these.
How did it go?
Go over there and inquire properly.
Ask carefully.
These bananas are really good.
Fully ripe.
So sweet.
Auntie,
for the past half month,
I've kept many words inside.
I'm done with it.,
Come on, taste this. See if it's soft.
It's fully ripe. Take a bite.
Not bad, huh?
Our family failed Jie.
Liu Yang is my younger brother.
If I scold him
for being poorly raised,
wouldn't that be a reprimand
to myself too?
He wasn't like this when he was little.
He would offer his little bowl of food
when he saw the puppy next door
starving.
How did he grow into what he is now?
Here we are, just the two of us chatting.
See, people all
have desires and emotions.
This is human nature.
Everyone has a good side and a bad side.
I'm not trying to defend my brother.
But the problem lies in that woman. She...
she already...
Right, huh?
I-It is a human life after all.
I'm really at my wits' end. Really.
Auntie,
do you think the blame's on me?
There is a family matter
that I've never told anyone.
When Liu Yang was little,
I once saw our dad
stealing rice and flour from home.
Our mom caught him
and lashed out at him.
He said it was for his mistress.
Auntie, do you think
this is what people call
"like father, like son"?
Maybe this is all my fault.
I knew that...
Wh-Where is my money?
What money?
What do you mean?
Why is my money gone?
-I need to buy food and cook for my kids.
-We are...
-We are chatting.
-No. Where's my money?
Look, it's all gone.
Auntie, are you having an episode?
-Where’s my money?
-You said you need... Calm down.
Don't panic.
Look, well...
Look.
I-Is this your money?
Is this yours? Look.
It's back, isn't it?
Right?
Just calm down.
Sit down and let's chat.
Finish the banana.
Where's the other fifty?
What do you mean by that?
There's another fifty-yuan bill.
How is there another one?
-I just gave you a fifty.
-I'm serious.
There should be another fifty.
Don't be like this.
How can you try to swindle me?
I-Isn't this it?
What the heck?
It's not. I only have some change
on me now.
-How could you try to swindle...
-I need it to buy food for my kids.
How could you try to swindle me?
Why did I even come
all the way here?
All the debts that little brat owes
are mine to pay now.
Am I fated to be this unlucky?
You... I...
Now I can't even pay the bus fare...
This is it.
Oh, look at that.
Alright then. Auntie,
eat some more.
This is not enough!
Look!
That's all I got. Knit your sweater.
Take care!
Now this is right.
Where's that money from earlier?
Anyone here?
I've told you many times.
I just didn't see him.
It's you.
Looking for your boss?
I'm here to have my hair washed.
A good number of people come here
looking for him every day.
My door handle's almost broken from that.
The police station is right next door.
Why don't they go seek help there?
Won't that be like a chicken
entering a wolf's den?
The police are also looking for Dong.
Why did Dong
just vanish into thin air?
Did he commit a crime or what?
I'm just an errand boy.
How am I supposed to know?
Haven't you thought
about asking Ms. Wan?
♪ In the first watch,
the crescent moon rises ♪
♪ The spirit drum booms,
resounding by the heavenly gate ♪
♪ Feet treading the Seven Star Step,
hands holding a peach wood basin ♪
♪ Stay not in the wild,
where frost bites deep ♪
♪ In the second watch, dark clouds roll ♪
♪ The spirit bells chime,
calling the three souls home ♪
♪ In the third watch,
clappers shake heaven and earth ♪
♪ All you brothers,
thank the gods for their grace ♪
Ms. Wan,
was Dong taken by the Yellow Immortal?
Don't you talk nonsense here.
The Yellow Immortal
said that Dong
isn't in Yuhong at all.
Then where is he now?
Well... I did a quick divination.
You should head south and look for him!
Got it.
Thank you, Ms. Wan!
Quick, guys!
What are you doing here?
You're making so much noise.
Officer Liu.
Do you think I can't see you
or what?
Am I blind to you?
Juan.
I heard
Liang Zhendong went missing. Is it true?
No, it's not true.
Dong is in seclusion.
Then why did you come here?
Just to ask Ms. Wan about him and have her
pass a message to him.
Can't you call him?
Is Wan Xiuhua more reliable
than China Mobile now?
Dong just has great trust in Ms. Wan.
How is your sister doing?
She called and said
she had arrived in Shanghai.
She told me not to go find her.
And you won't just because she said so?
How could you be this negligent?
She's a girl.
If she trips or falls on the road,
no one will be there to help her.
Are you really not worried?
Listen, Juan.
You know how my sister is.
She has never considered Tiecheng her home
growing up.
And she always talked about
going back to Shanghai.
This time, she left quietly.
I bet she was done being
a burden to my brother-in-law.
You still call Yang your brother-in-law?
Well...
My sister was the one
who insisted on the divorce.
It was Yang who failed your sister.
Don't say that, Juan.
I don't blame him,
and my sister won't let me
blame him either.
Well, if...
you ever see Liu Yang,
tell him
to come home for dinner.
May I come too?
Isn't that obvious?
Do I have to specially invite you?
Cut the crap already.
I'm going to work then, Juan.
I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Just be careful out there.
Mind your behavior.
You hear me?
Be steady.
Sure, got it.
Hao Jie has arrived in Shanghai
and is in hospital now.
The doctors there are highly competent.
So don't worry.
She'll definitely be cured.
Here you are.
Eat the apple.
Weiguo.